https://oklahomaskydiving.com/privacy/

Oklahoma Skydiving Center(918) 225-2222Gift CertificatesBook Now!First JumpTandem SkydivingTandem RatesVideo ServicesFAQsLearn To SkydiveLearn To SkydiveRatesFAQsExperienced SkydiversExperienced SkydiversBASE JumpingDropZoneDropZoneAircraftFacilitiesEventsAboutAboutMeet Our TeamExhibition TeamSkydiving ReviewsBlogGiving BackLocalLocalAccommodationsAttractionsRestaurantsContactContact UsDirections
PRIVACY POLICY: “We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.”SECURITY POLICY “Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number. Refund Policy All gift certificates are good for one year from the date purchased. All sales are final No Refunds.Delivery Policy “Please be assured that your gift certificate will be emailed to you within two days of purchase. If you require express delivery, please call us at 918-225-2222.Refund Policy All gift certificates are good for one year from the date purchased. All sales are final No Refunds.Stay ConnectedSign up to receive news and updates.First Name*Last Name*Email* PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Book Now!Site InfoHomeFirst JumpTandem SkydivingTandem RatesVideo ServicesFAQsLearn To SkydiveLearn To SkydiveRatesFAQsExperienced SkydiversExperienced SkydiversBASE JumpingDropZoneDropZoneAircraftFacilitiesEventsAboutAboutMeet Our TeamExhibition TeamSkydiving ReviewsBlogGiving BackLocalLocalAccommodationsAttractionsRestaurantsContactContact UsDirectionsWhere Am I?Oklahoma Skydiving CenterPrivacySitePrivacySitemapQuick LinksFirst Time SkydivingLearn To SkydiveBook NowPurchase Gift CertificatesContact Info#4 West Airport Road Cushing, OK 74023(918) 225-2222info@skydiveok.comSkydiving SafetyEach one of our skydiving instructors is thoroughly trained, highly experienced, and safety minded.Copyright © 2020, Oklahoma Skydiving Center, All Rights Reserved.DropZone Web Design & Marketing by Beyond Marketing, LLCBook Online Now!Buy Gift CertificatesContact Us (918) 225-2222 #4 West Airport Road •
Cushing, OK 74023 | Direction Tips Friday: 8am - 9pm | Hours HomeFirst JumpTandem SkydivingTandem RatesVideo ServicesFAQsLearn To SkydiveLearn To SkydiveRatesFAQsExperienced SkydiversExperienced SkydiversBASE JumpingDropZoneDropZoneAircraftFacilitiesEventsAboutAboutMeet Our TeamExhibition TeamSkydiving ReviewsBlogGiving BackLocalLocalAccommodationsAttractionsRestaurantsContactContact UsDirections
